<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2019 Community Media Conference</title>
    <link>https://canstream.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on 2019 Community Media Conference</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 00:19:13 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://canstream.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Citizen Journalism Workshop</title>
      <link>https://canstream.github.io/pages/citizen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 00:19:13 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://canstream.github.io/pages/citizen/</guid>
      <description>On Sunday 29th September at Salford Quays, the Community Media Association is delighted to partner with BBC MediaCityUK to programme this citizen journalism workshop event for the community media sector which is free to attend with refreshments and lunch provided.
10:00 - Arrival, registration, tea and coffee, networking
11:00 - Welcome &amp;amp; Introduction
11:15 - Workshop with Amanda Eleftheriades-Sherry of ClydesiderMag. Using creative community events as a catalyst for conversation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Agenda</title>
      <link>https://canstream.github.io/pages/agenda/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 00:18:32 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://canstream.github.io/pages/agenda/</guid>
      <description>The 2019 Community Media Conference will address a number of key themes:
 Production: radio production masterclass with Hindenburg Systems, radio presenting skills masterclass with Scruton Wyatt Media
 Small-scale digital audio broadcasting: tech, licensing, funding
 Sustainability: Community Radio Fund, Audio Content Fund
 Dialogue: inRadio discussions with leading industry figures and Decentered Media podcast recordings
  The outline Conference agenda is below (subject to change):
09:00 Registration and networking</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Location</title>
      <link>https://canstream.github.io/pages/location/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2019 23:56:25 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://canstream.github.io/pages/location/</guid>
      <description>Address: Quay House, BBC MediaCityUK, Salford, M50 2BH Salford Quays is less than four miles from Manchester city centre, 12 miles from Manchester airport and a short distance from the M60. The SatNav postcode is M50 2EQ. Bus, train and Metrolink information at www.tgfm.com. Please arrive promptly from 9am on the day in order to quickly clear security. Please bring photo identiifcation to speed your entry.
Parking Parking is available at The Lowry Outlet Mall.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>